<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mehedi Hasan Jibon</title>
    <link>//thisisjibon.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mehedi Hasan Jibon</description>
    <image>
      <url>//thisisjibon.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>//thisisjibon.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//thisisjibon.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//thisisjibon.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//thisisjibon.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hey there! 👋
I’m a final year undergraduate student at SUST, studying Computer Science and Engineering.
My primary interest lies in Human-Computer Interaction (HCI) research, where I am currently exploring ways to improve computer systems for neurodivergent usergroup. I’m also fascinated by Machine Learning (ML) systems and how they can enhance HCI.
You can check out my GitHub profile for some cool side projects I’ve worked on.
When I’m not geeking out over tech, you’ll find me listening to alternative rock music, binge-watching captivating TV dramas, or cheering for my favorite football team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infographics</title>
      <link>//thisisjibon.github.io/infographics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//thisisjibon.github.io/infographics/</guid>
      <description>I also create hand-drawn infographics and illustrations to summarize the key concepts in data science, machine learning and bioinformatics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coming Soon!</title>
      <link>//thisisjibon.github.io/blogs/soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//thisisjibon.github.io/blogs/soon/</guid>
      <description>Preview Exciting stuffs are coming soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serious-Manager</title>
      <link>//thisisjibon.github.io/projects/serious-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//thisisjibon.github.io/projects/serious-manager/</guid>
      <description>Overview Serious-Manager predicts optimal Fantasy Premier League team for a gameweek, suggests optimal transfer and best captain choice. We created a comprehensive time-series database of all premier league players, incorporated various prediction approaches like Neural Network, Random Forest, Decision Tree. Our approach surpassed average FPL manager&amp;rsquo;s score by scoring over 100%.
Features 📈 Remarkable Score Boost: Our approach surpassed average FPL manager score by over 100%, it reshapes the playing field, turning every matchday into an opportunity for success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UniManage</title>
      <link>//thisisjibon.github.io/projects/unimanage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//thisisjibon.github.io/projects/unimanage/</guid>
      <description>Overview UniManage is a web platform designed to streamline university administration processes. Our innovative approach includes a robust third normal form database architecture to ensure data integrity. With features like real-time results updates, convenient course registration, and personalized daily schedules, UniManage empowers universities to operate more efficiently and provide a seamless experience for students and faculty.
Features 📊 Efficient Database Design: At the core of UniManage lies a robust designed database structure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unraveling the Intersection of HCI and Neurodiversity in Bangladesh</title>
      <link>//thisisjibon.github.io/research/erpred/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//thisisjibon.github.io/research/erpred/</guid>
      <description>Overview In the enchanting realm where Human-Computer Interaction (HCI) meets the captivating tapestry of neurodiversity, our research project, &amp;ldquo;Unraveling the Intersection of HCI and Neurodiversity in Bangladesh,&amp;rdquo; seeks to illuminate new pathways of understanding and support for individuals with Attention-Deficit/Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD).
Semi-Structured Interviews: As explorers of human experiences, we embarked on a journey of discovery. Through semi-structured interviews with parents of children with ADHD and expert caregivers, we navigated the intricate web of attitudes, beliefs, and lived realities surrounding ADHD within the Bangladeshi cultural context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BanglaBeats: Enhancing Bangla Music Genre Classification</title>
      <link>//thisisjibon.github.io/research/acetylcholinesterase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//thisisjibon.github.io/research/acetylcholinesterase/</guid>
      <description>Overview In the vibrant world of music and machine learning, our project, &amp;ldquo;BanglaBeats,&amp;rdquo; emerges as a harmonious fusion of technology and culture. Focusing on the rich and diverse landscape of Bangla music, we embarked on a journey to enhance the accuracy and efficiency of Bangla music genre classification.
Comprehensive Dataset At the heart of our project lies a meticulously curated dataset of Bangla songs. Comprising 1617 data samples spanning across 8 distinct genres, it forms the foundation upon which our research thrives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classmate</title>
      <link>//thisisjibon.github.io/projects/classmate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//thisisjibon.github.io/projects/classmate/</guid>
      <description>Overview Classmate is a dynamic hub for educators and students to foster collaborative learning environment. This powerful tool seamlessly integrates class management with advanced database query functionalities, providing an all-in-one solution for educational communities.
Features 📚 Streamlined Class Management: With a user-friendly interface, Classmate empowers educators to efficiently manage classes, threads, and resources. With the help of using Builder Design Pattern and traditional Object-Oriented Programming concepts in its architecture, we ensured scalability and adaptability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My 1st post</title>
      <link>//thisisjibon.github.io/page/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//thisisjibon.github.io/page/</guid>
      <description>Desc Text.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
