<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Research on Mehedi Hasan Jibon</title>
    <link>https://thisisjibon.github.io/research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Research on Mehedi Hasan Jibon</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://thisisjibon.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://thisisjibon.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 23:15:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thisisjibon.github.io/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BanglaBeats: Enhancing Bangla Music Genre Classification</title>
      <link>https://thisisjibon.github.io/research/banglabeats/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thisisjibon.github.io/research/banglabeats/</guid>
      <description>Overview Music Genre Classification holds significant importance in the context of music content distribution platforms. In this study, we present BanglaBeats, a comprehensive dataset of Bengali songs. We also propose a CNN-based approach that surpasses previous CNN-based Bangla music genre classification approaches in terms of accuracy. We did not stop here. We explored the possibility of transformer-based approaches for Bengali music genre classification tasks. We fine-tuned DistiHubert and Wav2-Vec2-Base-960h models. Our results reveal that further optimization techniques can enhance this task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unraveling the Intersection of HCI and Neurodiversity in Bangladesh</title>
      <link>https://thisisjibon.github.io/research/adhd-intervention/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thisisjibon.github.io/research/adhd-intervention/</guid>
      <description>Overview ADHD is characterized as one of the most prevalent neurodevelopmental conditions worldwide. Children with ADHD face many cognitive challenges in the social and academic context. In this regard, we hypothesize about e-learning-based technological intervention. In this study, we address existing factors that impact the adoption of technological intervention and design an effective technological intervention for ADHD children in Bangladesh.
Semi-Structured Interview Before designing the intervention, we conducted a semi-structured interview with parents of ADHD children and professional caregivers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
