<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Researches on Mehedi Hasan Jibon</title>
    <link>//thisisjibon.github.io/research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Researches on Mehedi Hasan Jibon</description>
    <image>
      <url>//thisisjibon.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>//thisisjibon.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//thisisjibon.github.io/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unraveling the Intersection of HCI and Neurodiversity in Bangladesh</title>
      <link>//thisisjibon.github.io/research/erpred/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//thisisjibon.github.io/research/erpred/</guid>
      <description>Overview In the enchanting realm where Human-Computer Interaction (HCI) meets the captivating tapestry of neurodiversity, our research project, &amp;ldquo;Unraveling the Intersection of HCI and Neurodiversity in Bangladesh,&amp;rdquo; seeks to illuminate new pathways of understanding and support for individuals with Attention-Deficit/Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD).
Semi-Structured Interviews: As explorers of human experiences, we embarked on a journey of discovery. Through semi-structured interviews with parents of children with ADHD and expert caregivers, we navigated the intricate web of attitudes, beliefs, and lived realities surrounding ADHD within the Bangladeshi cultural context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BanglaBeats: Enhancing Bangla Music Genre Classification</title>
      <link>//thisisjibon.github.io/research/acetylcholinesterase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//thisisjibon.github.io/research/acetylcholinesterase/</guid>
      <description>Overview In the vibrant world of music and machine learning, our project, &amp;ldquo;BanglaBeats,&amp;rdquo; emerges as a harmonious fusion of technology and culture. Focusing on the rich and diverse landscape of Bangla music, we embarked on a journey to enhance the accuracy and efficiency of Bangla music genre classification.
Comprehensive Dataset At the heart of our project lies a meticulously curated dataset of Bangla songs. Comprising 1617 data samples spanning across 8 distinct genres, it forms the foundation upon which our research thrives.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
